♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Nothin' different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can
find la la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ Then we'll monitor
his mind la la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joe can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end la la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call
Cambot Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
- Hi, girls.
♪ Tom Servo ♪
- Looks good.
♪ Crow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science
facts la la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(vault doors slamming)
- Here, chicky, chicky.
Here, chicky, chicky, chicky.
- Hi, everybody.
Welcome to the
satellite of love.
You caught us in the
middle of one of Joel's
life simulation exercises.
Joel's pretending
to be a dairy farmer
from southern
Wisconsin, help us!
- Oh, what happened to you?
Well anyway, hi there folks.
You know, I've been having
trouble with velvetleaf,
cutworm, and foxtail.
And well, that's when
the representative
from Monsanto came
out to my farm.
He recommended a pre-emergent,
infertile mixture
of lorsban with
atrazine in a tank mix.
And I told him to
get off my land.
Here chicky, chicky, chicky.
- [Computer] Have you chores
done by commercial cycle,
which is in 15 seconds.
- Yes'm, oop, yup.
- Real life simulation,
call this what you may,
the fact is Joel's dressing
up robots as farm animals.
- Come on, it's milkin' time.
- Moo!
- [Computer] Commercial starting
in five, four, three, two,
- Come on.
- Commercial sign on.
- Yep, just as I thought.
These hens just
aren't producin'.
I'm gonna have to spray
y'all with insecticide.
(clucking)
(upbeat music)
See, yeah, yeah,
it really works.
You can cut off a chicken's
head and it'll still run
all over the place.
Another fun thing to do on
the farm is cow tipping.
- Moo!
- Gee, there's a lot of time
to kill on a farm, isn't there?
- Yeah.
- Would you mind reuniting
my head with my body,
please, Joel Bob?
- Who said that?
- Old Joel Robinson had a farm?
- E-I-E-I don't think so.
- Well, never before
has the term booby
been more appropriate.
Why don't you tell them about
the invention exchange, Frank?
- Well, when you're on the
go kind of a guy like myself,
sometimes you need ear drops,
sometimes you need eye drops,
sometimes you need nose
drops, sometimes you need
throat drops, sometimes
when you touch,
the honesty's too much,
I want to hold you--
- Oh, shut up, Frank!
Look, carrying all those
medications around, granted,
is an inconvenience.
That's why I say combine them.
That's why we
invented the orbital,
auto-rhino-laryngological
dropper.
It very conveniently
combines all the ear, nose
and throat medications you
need into a convenient package.
(groaning)
What do you think, farm boy?
- Well, this is perfect
because after your invention
makes people feel better, they
can enjoy their good health
by going to the park and
enjoying this new invention.
It's called the musical chair.
(xylophone music)
Get it?
- Snappy.
- Yeah, what better
way to sit in
with your favorite musicians?
Sit in with the, because
it's a chair and uh...
- What do you think, sirs?
- Eh, I thought
it had no texture.
Say what's the ladder for?
- Well Frank, we've got a
very special guest today
to tell Joel and the bots
about today's experiment.
It's someone we
all know and love.
I think you're
going to be excited.
Ladies and gentleman,
Mr. Jack Perkins.
- Jack Perkins, wow!
- Hello, today's experiment
is called "Fugitive Alien",
a wonderful film from Japan.
Not to be confused
with The Fugitive,
the classic television series
which can be seen weekdays
right here on A&E.
This is actually a
strung together series
of Japanese shows,
which when put together in
this way, make for what I think
is some of the best
TV has to offer.
- Thanks Jack, now we--
- Then, Joyce Carol
Oates will be out to read
from her wondrous
new work of fiction.
Her first novel in
well over a month.
Then, Peter, Paul and Mary will
be out to give us a wondrous
rendition from one of
their songs off their
scintillating new album.
Then Hume Cronyn and Jessica
Tandy will be out to tell us
some poignant stories of the
joys and sorrows of being
really, really, horribly old.
And then Topel will be out.
- Oh, we got movies sir.
Who's Jack Perkins?
(clucking)
- [Joel] Okay,
that's good you guys,
- [Crow] Hey, it's
The Name of the Rose.
- [Joel] No, it's the smiling
face gone horribly awry!
- [Tom] Oh, oh.
- [Crow] Sandy Frank presents
her own personal hell!
- [Tom] Indeed!
- [Joel] Who is that guy?
- [Tom] Coy honnus, can't see!
Oh, never mind.
- [Crow] Aw man, cool, this
is just like episode 38
of Star Trek, the first
season, but it doesn't have
that same kind of--
- [Tom] No, no, no, it's
like the star raider that
the Daleks had in the fifth
generation of the Doctor,
the Doctor Who when they had
the three doctors together
and they had the one
that looked like Mo.
- [Crow] No it's
definitely like a Klingon.
- [Joel] Staring David
Jensen of Mars searching
for the one-armed alien.
- [Tom] The traffic on the
outbound orbital planet is heavy
a little on grange two
folks, you might try taking
an alternate grange
this morning.
- [Crow] Hey, quit
passin' on the right.
That's not fair.
- [Tom] Hmm, neat.
- [Crow] Tateyama and shove it!
- [Joel] Hey.
- [Tom] Cool, so.
(all screaming)
- [Tom] Don't do that!
- [Crow] Originally
produced for the stage
by the Royal
Shakespeare Company.
- [Joel] Watch out for that.
- [All] Tree!
- [Tom] Oh, just park
it anywhere, boys.
Oh just, ow.
- [Man] Here come the raiders.
Run for your lives.
- [Tom] Oh no, raid!
- [Crow] Oh, this is super
cool, like that first episode
of Battle Star Galactica when
they have to leave the planet
and Jane Seymour got
stabbed in the back.
- [Tom] It's like Invasion
Earth and they'll be like Zola
babies when the fast space
ships come in and they--
- [Crow] Nuh-uh.
- [Joel] Madame Butterfly?
- Attack!
- [Tom] We've
started already, sir.
- [Crow] Banana Peel!
- [Man] Come on to the shelters.
Run, run!
- [Tom] Oh, I'll catch up.
- Destroy the Earth
and its inhabitants.
- [Joel] It's heckraiser!
(exploding)
- [Crow] Hey, it's the
Rolling Stones hotel room.
- [Tom] I think it kind
of looks like Morton Thigh
in the early days.
(Crow laughing)
- [Crow] Why do they
need so many writers?
- [Tom] Oh, they need one
guy for the verbs, one guy
for the nouns, one guy for
the adjectives, you know,
adverbs and guns.
Whoa!
Ooh!
It looks like the
Florida/Tokyo stock exchange
on Black Monday, doesn't it?
- [Crow] Ah, they've broken
into Carol Channing's house.
(glass shattering)
- [Tom] Jin kata!
- [Joel] In color.
Wiggly poo, do the wiggly poo!
- [Crow] Aah, I've been
killed by an action figure!
- [Tom] Run, more credits, run!
- [Crow] Hey, no
cuttin' in line!
(grunting)
- [Tom] Jin kata.
Jin kata.
- [Joel] You're not half bad.
- You're all right, Ken.
Honestly, I've never
seen anyone so strong.
- [Crow] Certainly
not a red head.
- I'm twice as strong
back home on Valnastar.
- [Tom] Say, if
you don't shower.
- Did you hear that Ken?
I'll check it out.
- [Crow] How humiliating,
Earth taken over
by Judy Garland impersonators.
- [Joel] Ooh, spring
break pool jumping dude.
Kick man, you're not
gonna make it cool.
(grunting)
- [Crow] Bless you.
Heal or not.
- [Joel] Intriguing mix of
genocide and modern dance.
- [Crow] Hey, you're
starting to sound like
Jack Perkins, Joel.
- Ken, there's one.
- [Tom] When Josie and
the Pussycats go bad.
- Bang, bang, bang,
bang, bang, bang!
- Oh, there you go.
- You're dead!
- [Tom] Not yet.
- Bang, bang, bang.
- [Joel] Well, you
have split ends.
- Ken, little boys with guns
grow up to be big enemies.
Better kill him while
he's still young.
- Hey, do you want to play?
- [Woman] Ken!
- Hey, is everybody named Ken?
- Where are you, Ken?
- [Joel] What gives,
planet of the Kens or what?
- [Woman] Ken!
- [Crow] Planet where Kens are.
- [Tom] Oh, what a
perfect apocalyptic
jump suit she's wearing.
- Darling, where are you?
Ken!
- [Tom] Wait a minute.
- [Joel] Pink hearts, blue
moons, green Japanese boys.
- [Tom] What is this, Don
Kirshner's rock concert
all of a sudden?
- [Woman] Ken!
- Mama!
Mama!
- Don't kill my son,
please don't hurt him!
- [Joel] These
Obsession ads are weird.
- [Tom] Between Ken
and Ken lies Obsession.
- [Soldier] Shoot
Ken, kill them both!
- [Crow] Which Ken?
- [Joel] The closer Ken
gets, the better Ken looks.
- [Soldier] Ken, what
are you waiting for?
- [Tom] Uh-oh, buck fever.
- [Crow] Yep.
- [Joel] Only Ken's Ken
dresser knows for sure.
- [Crow] Ken two help Ken one.
- [Ken] Mama!
- [Tom] They have such
a glow about them.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- [Crow] His Mama is a saint.
- [Tom] If I have one life to
live, let me live it as a Ken.
- Don't shoot!
- [All] Don't shoot!
- [Tom] Spaz!
- [Soldier] Traitor!
- [Ken] I don't kill
women and children.
- [Soldier] Then stand
back and let me do it!
- [Ken] I said move!
- [Crow] You're a
disgrace to all Kens.
- [Joel] Was that you?
- Ken, Ken?
Why?
- [Tom] I love you Ken.
- You betrayed us, traitor.
- [Crow] Ah, the name's
Ken, call me Ken.
- [Announcer] You won't
get away with it, Ken.
- [Tom] Run Ken,
run, Ken kill Ken.
- [Announcer] Get him, he
killed one of his own men.
- I didn't mean to,
it was an accident.
- [Tom] Ken 33, go left,
Ken 16 and 18, flank him.
Ken seven go around the back.
Ken four, I mean, 10-four.
(laughs) I got confused.
- There he goes!
There!
He's a traitor, don't
let him get away!
- [Crow] Just like that
episode where it was like
the Nazi world on Star Trek.
- [Tom] No, no, no,
it was like Doctor Who
when Tom Baker was the Doctor.
He was the fifth Doctor and
he was trying to save Neela
from the Clite Masters.
- No, 'cause I saw it
at a math tournament.
- [Tom] No, no cause I saw
it in the Who Festival.
They had 12 hours.
- [Crow] He hurt
his little pants.
- [Soldier] After
him, he's been hit.
- [Crow] In the pants.
- [Tom] Little pants.
- You have betrayed us.
You will never set eyes
on Valnastar again.
- [Tom] Oh, I flipped and
I didn't even have to.
I just love to do
it, just for fun.
(panting)
- [Joel] What?
- [Tom] Hmm?
- [Joel] It smells
like my wig in here.
- I'll get home somehow.
(engine roaring)
- [Crow] Do you
want to go faster?
- You will not reach
home, all traitors die.
- [Tom] Don't smoke.
(chuckling)
You gotta get that
steering column fixed.
Oh oh oh!
- I'll get there if it's
the last thing I do.
- [Tom] Probably will be.
(upbeat music)
- The rangers.
- [Tom] Hey Boo-boo,
it's the Rangers.
- So they think they can
blow me out of the sky.
- [Tom] Yep.
- This lever is stuck.
- [Tom] So is the lever.
Lever broke.
- I can't get it under control.
- [Crow] I'm a crappy
special effect.
- Oh no.
- [Joel] Oh, yes.
- [Tom] Oh, yes.
- I don't want to die in
the middle of nowhere.
- [Joel] I want to die
in the thong section
of Victoria Secret.
- [Tom] Good call.
(moaning)
- [Joel] Pull up, pull up.
Oh boy.
He's in more trouble than
Hudson Hawk at the box office.
(chuckles)
- Yep.
- That's an alien sound.
- [Tom] Say.
- Enemy signal.
- [Crow] Or a garbage
truck backin' up.
- [Tom] Yeah, could be.
- They think they can
kill me so easily.
Well they're in for
a little surprise!
I'm a ranger too,
I'm a Star Wolf.
- [Joel] Of course you are, Ken.
Just keep saying
that to yourself.
(chanting)
- Monks in space!
- It's my only chance, I'm
gonna have to bail out.
- [Tom] Wait a
minute, is that Ken?
- [Crow] It's not Ken, it's Ken.
- [Tom] Oh, you mean Ken?
- [Crow] You're
confusing him with Ken.
- [Tom] Oh, I was
thinkin' of Ken.
- [Crow] No, Ken.
- [Tom] Ken, I thought
it was Ken all along.
(chanting)
- [Crow] Now let's
see, triple A road map,
flashlight, Mars bar, I'm set.
- [Tom] You know, some
people will do anything
to get to mass on Holy
Thursday, I gotta tell you.
- [Crow] Hey, he shouldn't
have had those baked beans.
(laughs) It's too easy.
- [Tom] Was that him or the?
- [Joel] I told you to
watch the speed bumps.
- What do you suppose that was?
- [Tom] It sounded like Ken.
- [Crow] Ken.
- What's happening here?
- Easy Tammy.
- Uh-huh, that was no meteorite.
- [Crow] That was my wife.
(mimicking drum roll)
- Turn on the
radiation deflector.
- [Joel] That trick never works.
- Operating, sir.
- That explosion sent out
powerful magnetic fields,
- [Tom] And so do I.
- It can destroy the spacecraft
if we're not careful.
So stay on the alert.
- Yes, sir!
- [Crow] Bless all
the Kens everywhere.
- [Tom] This is a sneeze
magnified 100 times.
(sneezing)
- [Joel] Do you smell aliens?
- Looks like we're
out of danger now.
- Uh-huh.
- Captain, what's
that out there?
- [Tom] It's a Xenith
Chromacolor and it
can be all yours
if you pick what's
behind door number one!
- [Ken] A man floating
through space.
- You're right.
- [Crow] It's a man
with little pants.
- [Tom] It's Frank Poole.
- He must have bailed out of
that ship before it exploded.
Looks like he's still breathing.
- [Joel] Good eye.
- Rocky?
- [Pilot] Yes, sir?
- [Dan] We're going
to rescue him.
- I don't think that's
a very good idea.
Why don't we just leave
well enough alone?
- Don't say that.
- He's isn't even
wearing a space suit.
No way he could've
survived out there.
- He could've!
Dan, what is our mission
if not to save lives?
- You know she's right.
Okay, let's go for it, Rocky.
- Yes, sir.
- [Tom] Again?
(whirring)
- [Crow] Whoa, take your
foot off the clutch.
- [Ken] That's not
the wolf attacker.
Who could it be?
- [Tom] Oh, I remember this.
This is just like in
Marooned when David Janssen
goes to save Gene Hackman
and James Franciscus
in the derelict spaceship
before the Soviet--
- [Crow] Yeah,
that's pretty cool.
- [Tom] Yeah and the Soviet
satellite comes up and--
- [Ken] I guess I've had it.
- [Joel] Space Mimes, in color.
- [Crow] He's got
the monkey bars.
- [Tom] Doctor
Levinson I presume?
- [Crow] Give me a
hug, you big galoot.
(Crow mimicking kisses)
- [Woman] He's alive all right.
- [Joel] I got dibs.
- [Dan] I don't get
it, nobody could have
survived that explosion.
- [Dan] You're right.
Any normal human being would
have been blown to bits.
- [Joel] Ooh!
- [Ken] He's coming to.
- [Crow] Terms with himself.
(Joel laughing)
- [Joel] Oh.
My God I've been
captured by Wayne Newton.
- [Crow] Danke schoen.
- [Dan] Hello friend.
- [Joel] Ow!
- Welcome to the Earth's
oldest space ship Bacchus-3.
- [Tom] Model A.
- My name is Joe.
- [Joel] Hello Joe,
what do you know?
- [Tom] Just got
back from Kokomo.
- How did you ever
survive that crash?
- Watch it Ken, this
might be a trap.
You sure took your chances
out there without a spacesuit.
- [Joe] Or did your
spacesuit explode as well?
- [Tom] (laughs) Good one, sir.
- I just don't get it.
- [Tom] Can't a guy get a
cup of coffee around here?
- Listen.
- I'll answer that, sir.
(alarm buzzing)
This is Bacchus-3 over.
- [Space Control]
This is Space Control.
The Wolf Raiders from Valnastar
have been attacking the earth.
- [All] Huh, huh, huh, huh?
Aw.
- [Space Control]
660 on the alert!
(grunting)
- [Tom] Whoa, that's
a strong reaction.
Seems a little defensive
to me, doesn't he?
- Cut it out you guys.
Cut it out.
- [Joel] Shines.
- [Ken] Can't afford
to lose control.
- [Crow] Yeah well, what
do you call that then?
- [Joel] Aww, you
could see the zipper.
(groaning)
- [Tom] I thought so,
my best flat wear.
- I've got a couple
of questions.
- [Crow] Do you
like Peter Allen?
- Who are you?
- [Tom] And what's the
capital of South Dakota?
- And why did you react that way
when you heard the
word wolf, huh?
And where did you get
all your strength?
- You'd better tell
us the truth, fella.
- [Tom] Come on, come on!
- I'm an astronomer.
I was doing scientific work.
- Huh?
- You're hurting me, let go.
I heard about the Wolf
Raiders on my radio.
That's why I reacted.
- I think he's telling
us the truth, sir.
- [Joel] I also
believe in fairies.
- I don't wanna get killed.
- Captain, UFOs on
our radar screen!
- [Crow] I'm busy can't you see?
- Check it.
- Yes sir.
Let's go.
- Right.
- [Tom] Right!
Nice cuff links.
- [Joel] Pierre Cardin.
Now we're gonna
spank you big time.
- I don't want you to
move from this spot.
Unless of course you feel
like leaving this ship
and floating in space.
- [Crow] You can get up now.
- [Joel] Well, it seem
comfortable but jeepers.
- [Crow] Huh?
(whirring)
(beeping)
- [Tom] Hey, look that
truck's headed to Utah.
- You keep your
eyes on the screen.
- [Woman] Yes sir.
- All instruments operational?
- Yes sir.
- [Crow] And how.
- We're approaching
route MMS 600, sir.
- [Joel] And my heart is racing.
- Look how fast they're going.
Who can generate that
kind of velocity?
- Wolf Raiders
- [Tom] I can.
- For sure.
- [Crow] (sniffs)
You smell good.
- [Pilot] Sir I don't think
we're any match for them.
- [Crow] Got my nose.
- Look at that!
(Crow mumbling)
- Change course!
You can't take them on in
this beat up old crate.
Change course!
- Someone put a
gag in his mouth.
- [Tom Joe And Crow]
I'll do it, I'll do it!
- [Tom] I got it!
- He's talking sense for once.
They have greater firing power.
This ship is much too old
to take on superior forces
like Wolf Raiders.
- It's too late to
turn around now.
I think they've
spotted our position.
- [Crow] They're bat men.
- [Joel] Are they
listening to ELO?
- Here they come.
- [Crow] It's a fleet
of drapery hooks.
- [Joel] Are you a good
witch or a bad witch?
- This is it.
- [Tom] Let's go.
Hey, a got an idea.
Let's get that box of
hats out of the back.
- [Crow] Oh, I know where
that is, I'll get it.
- At the parts--
- What are you two
yard monkeys doin' now?
- Well, seein' the stupid
Wolf Raider hair helmets
in the experiment reminded
me of all this stuff
from the last hat party we had.
Hey, put that one on.
- Yeah.
- Oh, no I don't
wanna, I'd feel silly.
- I remember that one, that
one was the grandest of all.
- Yeah, yeah, I thought we
could take some of these
and have fun with them,
and maybe make up even more
stupider hats, you know,
for the next party.
- Oh say, put that one on
me, I got an idea here.
- Okay.
- Now you see this is
a helmet for astronauts
who are losing their hair.
(Crow laughing)
When you see Mr.
Balding call him over.
- That's a good idea.
- Okay, all right,
I'm into it now.
Look at this one, this
goes back to 1981.
I'm a punk from space, get it?
- Ooh.
♪ I am an anarchist ♪
Get it?
- Oh, that's cool, hey,
this big one over here.
Put this one on me, Joel.
- Okay.
- Now I got, I got it.
This is what Patti
Labelle would look like
on the space shuttle.
♪ Wah ♪
(laughing)
- Yeah!
- Wow, that's cool.
- try that other
one there, okay.
- Oh, way down there.
- Oh, oh, watch the hand.
- Sorry yeah.
Oh, wow look it, it's the
Ted Koppel satellite of hair.
- Or, you can pull
down the curl in front
and it would look just
like Frank's hair helmet.
(Crow laughing)
- Oh, I think those
things are wonderful.
(all laughing)
- Push the button, Frank.
- Doctor F you better
come have a look at this.
Joel and the bots are
making fun of my hair.
My hair!
- Now Frank, let them
have their little fun.
The experiment's not quite
over and they'll soon live
to regret it.
(all laughing)
- [Crow] Oh, rich.
- Oh, wait, hey guys,
look at this one, hey.
(grunting)
This one looks like Doctor
Forrester if his head got sucked
into the vacuum of
space through a keyhole.
(laughing)
- Now you cut that out.
Remember what I said
about hat parties.
You get your little hinders
back into that theater
and you watch the film.
I'm not amused by your
antics in the least.
- I thought it was
a sheer delight.
I think that's about as
grand as a hat party can get.
(buzzing)
(groaning)
That was about as
painful as a cattle prod
to the shoulder could get.
(buzzing)
- Send him commercial, Frank.
- I'll send them
commercial sign.
- [Jack] But later
on in the program,
Linda Ellerbee will be out.
(buzzing)
(groaning)
(lively music)
- [Joe] I hate to say it but
Jack Perkins had that coming.
- Oh, yeah, poor guy.
- That party never
ended like that before.
- You're crazy!
- [Tom] Ooh.
Ooh.
(coughs)
- [Crow] I'm exhausted.
(mimicking ship engine)
- [Joel] I wish
someone would turn off
the courageous cat music.
- [Tom] Chili
peppers burn my gut.
(singing)
- [Crow] Ooh, chin rascal.
- [Tom] More like face rascal.
- [Crow] Space speed.
- [Joel] Edward Munch I presume?
- [Tom] (laughs) Look at that.
- [Joel] Giving
him a face massage.
- [Crow] Well we can't
fight 'em but we can confuse
the heck out of 'em.
(dramatic music)
Fries are up.
- [Tom] Yep.
(beeping)
- [Joel] Whoa, that was us.
Jeepers.
- [Tom] Somebody
hang up the phone.
Now watch out for that, ugh!
Well, never mind.
- [Crow] Oops.
- Cease fire.
Bacchus-3, you haven't
seen the last of me.
- [Crow] Jim Bacchus?
(laughing)
(beeping)
- [Joel] Uh, cookies
are done sir.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Cool, huh?
- [Joel] Yeah, good music
- Looks like we made it.
- [Tom] Left each other
all the way into a knuckle.
- That's for knockin'
out my officer.
Look alive, you guys,
there's work to do.
- [Tom] I'm alive, sir.
- [Crow] I'm sorry
honey, are you okay?
- [Joe] Rocky, are you
okay, say something.
- [Tom] Yo Adrian,
cut me, cut me.
- We did it, we
got away from them.
- [Joel] I did,
yeah I did. (laughs)
- Who is this guy?
- All I know is he's 10
times as strong as we are.
- [Tom] And I love him.
- [Joe] And he got us
through the Wolf
Raiders single handedly.
- [Tom] A snappy dresser
and a good friend.
Hey bookmobile, summer
reading program.
- [Crow] Third planet from the
sun will be known as Earth.
Pretty much.
- [Tom] Oh no, we'll
have to circle LaGuardia
for an hour I'm bettin'.
- [Joel] Hey, I can
see the Great Wall.
- [Crow] It's okay.
(sings)
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] They're goin'
to the Dells, cool.
- [Joel] Jimmy left his
Legos in the driveway again.
- [Tom] That kid.
You know, I tell you, that
ship is burping out a lot
of chlorofluorocarbons there.
Punchin' a hole in the ozone.
(Crow coughing)
- Attention please--
- [Joel] The bank will be
closing in five minutes.
- Landing station 14.
- Here is the latest report
on the attack on
the Valna Raiders.
Due to heavy damage,
aerospace port number six
has been closed to all
traffic until further notice.
- That's our port.
- [Ken] What'll we do?
- I just talked to headquarters.
They said all streets leaving
the base have been destroyed.
- Check that out.
- [Tom] Check her out.
- [Joel] Hey.
- [Announcer] Attention please.
- Take charge of the prisoner.
- Yes, sir.
- [Announcer] Flights are
kindly requested to proceed
immediately to Space Command
headquarters for debriefing.
We repeat, senior officers
of all incoming flights
proceed at once to Space
Command headquarters.
- [Crow] Watch the steno
pool go wild for his vinyl.
- Excuse me?
- Sir?
- How can I contact
space port six?
- Right up there, sir.
- Thank you.
- [Tom] I just wanna check
out my car loan here.
Get out of my way.
(beeping)
- [Crow] Alt function.
(ominous music)
- [Tom] Huh?
- [Joel] Noah's Ark?
- [Tom] At the door.
- [Crow] Hey and
there's Moses' Jeep.
- [Tom] Ooh!
- Did he tell you how
he got that wound?
- [Crow] I gave it to him.
- He refused to answer
any of our questions.
He started shouting
and acting crazy.
So I gave him a
tranquilizer to quiet him.
- Is he likely to get violent?
- He's highly unpredictable.
Please maintain him
here under heavy guard.
- Thanks for the warning.
- Good-bye.
Come on.
- [Tom] Everybody's doing
their banking in this movie.
- [Joel] Looks
like Ken's driving
the Malibu Barbie beach jeep.
- [Tom] I just have to get out
some money for the weekend.
Aww dang, they're closed, boy
I would love to be a banker.
- [Joel] So, dinner
Thursday, great.
Excuse me.
- Get out of my way.
Beat it.
Hi say, dinner
Friday, great, okay.
- [Crow] Oh hi, dinner
Sunday, can we do it?
Oh, you're free.
- [Joel] Ladies and
gentlemen, this is Elvis.
- [Crow] Thank you,
thank you very much, huh?
- [Tom] The audience has
left the arena. (laughing)
- [Joel] What the, oh, huh?
- [Tom] Baby doll,
ballet slippers.
Huh, a geometric nucleus?
And a chew toy.
- [Crow] Well, I'll just
rifle the dead's stuff here.
- [Joel] So dinner Sunday?
(groaning)
- What a gaff.
(sad music)
- Maryanne?
- [Tom] Ginger, Skipper,
Lovey, Professor.
- [Crow] Thank you,
thank you very much.
- Barbara?
- [Joel] Did he say Whopper?
- [Tom] Sounded like Whopper.
- Is that a pet name?
- Oh darling!
Darling, where's Maryanne?
- [Crow] Dead,
dusting downstairs.
- [Barbara] Where is she?
- Maryanne's resting.
- [Crow] In peace.
- [Tom] Pieces.
- Oh, thank goodness.
I was so worried something
had happened to her
in that terrible attack.
- [Tom] Yeah, whatever.
- I couldn't find her
anywhere, then I passed out
and woke up here.
- [Tom] What'd you
say, what a view.
You got a great room here.
- [Barbara] Now we're
all together again.
(Barbara gasping)
(ominous music)
- [Joel] Well, that does
take the pressure off.
- [Tom] Yeah.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Hey, Ken's
got a problem.
- [Tom] Ken wasn't careful.
Ken's going to get candy.
- Oh no you don't!
- [Doctor] Please
sir, you mustn't.
- [Tom] Oh, yes I do, physician
heal thyself. (laughs)
(tense music)
- [Joel] I know just what to do.
I'll sneak out of here
disguised as Chad Everett.
- [Tom] That always works.
- [Crow] Hey,
McGarret's up here.
- [Tom] Ooh, Toughskins in
husky, slim and regular.
- [Joel] Ken's out
cross-training, just do it.
- [Announcer] Ken was
safe for the moment,
but where could he go?
What could he do?
Outcast on his own planet.
A fugitive alien on earth.
He would have to make a
fresh start somewhere.
- [Crow] In the robot holocaust.
- [Announcer] Where, and
how could he get there?
- [Crow] And what of
Bob's love for Chad?
(engine roaring)
- [Tom] Sorry, that
was me, excuse me.
- [Ken] A spacecraft.
- [Joel] Duh.
- I'll have to hijack one.
- [Joel] (laughs) Better.
- [Crow] Not in those slacks.
(singing)
- [Joel] Now, now, I cue myself,
jump back and ha, jumping,
running and spinning.
- [Tom] Follow me, follow me.
Oh, I'm over here, careful.
(Tom panting)
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
nine, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16, 17.
- [Joel] This is
good for the glutes.
- [Tom] Push, push guys.
The burn, the burn. (panting)
- [Joel] He's at a ski
lodge now, what gives?
- [Tom] Excuse me,
can you tell me where
I could hijack a
spaceship anybody?
Okay, never mind.
Anybody?
Spaceship?
I need to hijack a spaceship.
Say!
- [Ken] Nobody around,
but how do I get aboard?
- [Tom] Go through
the lumber yard.
That's how you get a board,
get it, I said lumber?
- Hello, stranger.
- [Crow] Hi, sailor.
- Did you just drop by for
coffee or are were you planning
to stay on for
the cocktail hour?
- [Crow] Huh?
I'll have that cocktail now.
- Well friend, you're not
a very gracious guest.
- [Crow] I've brought crackers.
- It isn't very courteous
to point a gun at your host.
- [Joel] It's not courteous
to point your finger--
- You shouldn't have run away
from that nice clean infirmary.
How about--
- St. James infirmary.
- [Joe] Giving me the gun?
- That's enough.
Turn around and face the wall.
- [Joel] The wall?
- Go on!
(Joe laughing)
- [Joe] Don't you think
it'd be a good idea
to check if it's loaded?
- What?
(grunting)
- [Joel] Room 235,
works every time.
- [Crow] Honest, Joel.
- Stupidest thing I ever
did was to save the life
of a Valna Raider, You people
have no respect for life!
You'd even kill your
own families if it
brought you some advantage.
The world will never be safe
with people like you around!
- [Joel] Let's kiss.
- Look, you'd even
destroy the universe!
Look in.
The minute I saw you, I
knew you were one of those
savage Valna Wolves.
- [Tom] But I loved you!
(lively music)
- You know something,
that was my last flight.
I wanted to devote the rest
of my life to my wife and kid.
My wife just died in my arms!
- [Crow] Hey, you were
way over by the window.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- Honestly, where's the pride
in killing defenseless
women and children?
You call that heroism?
- [Crow] I call it fun,
don't you have any hobbies?
- When we saved you, a
little swatch of cloth
got torn off your uniform.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- I found one exactly like it
next to the body of
my little daughter!
What have you got to say?
- [Tom] Oops, I'm sorry?
- I'm listening!
- Ah!
(shouting)
- [Crow] No one can
beat me at snap zooms.
I was in Time of the Apes.
- There's no point
trying to hide it.
I was on a mission.
But I killed one of my
comrades in an accident.
I ran away.
- [Tom] Nice lips.
- Now the other Wolves
are hunting the traitor.
- You're lying
through your teeth.
You expect me to buy that?
- It's the truth, I swear it!
Now listen to the
rest of the story!
- [Tom] Page two.
- We attacked Earth.
My buddy ordered
me to kill a child.
- [Joel] They never
explain the blonde wigs.
I don't get that.
- I couldn't and it was then
that he turned his rifle
on the child.
Then I saw him raise
his gun to fire.
I just wanted to get him
to put the rifle down.
(zapping)
Suddenly, I looked down
and saw that glassy look
in his eyes.
- [Tom] That sly,
come-hither stare.
- I'd forgotten
how strong I was.
- Ken, you did the right thing.
- [Joel] Now turn
off the chants.
- The world is mad.
You know I never keep
any bullets in my gun.
- [Crow] Like Barney Fife.
- The thought of killing
anyone is too horrible.
I didn't feel that way
when I was about your age.
I was like you,
wild and reckless.
- [Joel] That's me to a T.
- Until today you
killed for kicks.
- [Crow] Hey, like
the "Wild Rebels".
- You were just like I used
to be, a thrill killer.
- I wasn't, I was a soldier
carrying out orders!
There's no dishonor in that!
- [Joe] What is dishonor then?
Killing for a corrupt power?
- [Joel] Punky cheeks.
- [Joe] You betrayed
your own country.
(grunting)
(chanting)
- You betrayed us, you traitor.
- [Crow] See that's why
you're a scummy traitor.
- Cigar.
- [Tom] Why, yes it is.
(Joe laughing)
- I've been thinking
things over.
No point in retiring now
with no wife or
family to go home to.
- [Joel] You'll do fine.
- You know, I'm going to need
some new men in the crew.
- [Crow] Slim-hipped
and willowy.
- [Tom] Big lips.
- Young fella who's
become a fugitive.
Who's being hunted
all over the universe.
- [Tom] Who could that be?
- Could do a lot worse
than throwing in his lot
with the crew of Bacchus-3.
- [Tom] Hm.
- We might even
get to be friends.
- [Crow] He asked
me, he asked me!
- I don't understand, what
have a I done to deserve this?
- We don't deserve
half the things we get.
(laughing)
You're stuck here!
Listen.
- [Tom] Mood swings, boy.
- Do exactly what I tell you
and you have a good chance
of turning into a man,
not just a Wolf Raider.
(Tom growling)
And don't you ever forget.
- [Tom] What?
- I know exactly who you
are and where you came from.
- [Tom] Oh.
- One false move and
I'll set you adrift
to fend for yourself.
- [Woman] Captain!
- [Joel] Now let's
have some fun.
- Now then.
- [Woman] Captain!
- Whether you like it or not.
- [Tom] She's yours.
- It looks like
you just signed on.
- [Crow] Welcome to Herbalife.
(dramatic music)
- Captain Joe.
(Ken laughing)
I kinda think I'll like it.
- [Crow] Yeah, whatever, idiot.
- [Joel] Let's go skiing gang.
- Everything's fine.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] In the land of Dairy
Queen, we treat you right.
- [Narrator] While
Ken was being welcomed
aboard Bacchus-3 and starting
his life as an earthling,
back on Valnastar, Ken's
former home, the Wolf Raiders
were returning from their
unsuccessful mission.
- [Crow] Backstory.
- [Narrator] Their leader,
the notorious Lord Halkun,
who was determined
to punish Ken mercilessly
for his supposed betrayal.
- [Tom] Meanwhile, I went
to more voiceover auditions.
- [Joel] Say, speak of
punishing mercilessly, whoa.
(whistling)
- [Crow] I'm wearing a
bib 'cause I just ate.
- [Tom] Tragedy
tomorrow, kabuki tonight.
- I take it you have already
heard that your brother
has lost his life.
- Yes.
- He was killed by Ken.
- Ken did it?
- [Tom] Those bastards.
- Why, that can't be true.
- I know it must
seem impossible.
You loved each other, and he
was your brother's friend.
I trusted him too.
How sad it is to put
your trust in a traitor.
And that's not the worst part.
He killed your brother in an
attempt to defend an earthling.
- [Joel] Oops.
- [Tom] Now, we'll never
get my records back.
- Then he escaped into the
unknown in a stolen spaceship.
- [Joel] That'll happen.
- He's a coward and a traitor,
he has disgraced us all.
- [Crow] I forbid
you to see him.
- He has forfeited
the right to live.
- Must he die?
- [Halkun] Yes and you
must be his executioner.
It is an old Valna law that
murders must be avenged
by the victim's next of kin.
- [Tom] Not that I don't
trust you, oh wise one,
but can I see the
book on that rule?
- [Crow] Rat Patrol, in color.
- [Joel] You know, it looks
like they were shooting this
out of the windshield of a
Vista Cruiser station wagon.
- [Tom] Yeah, tinted.
- [Halkun] Ken must
die by your hand.
You are not to return
here without his head.
Without his head.
- [Joel] Oh, I gotta
lay off the 'shrooms.
- Ken.
- [Crow] Did someone say Ken?
- Ken, you will pay
dearly for what you did.
- [Joel] I know, Mama.
- [Crow] Oh!
- [Tom] Well, that was easy.
I can go home, oh damn,
I was supposed to bring
back his head.
- [Woman] Ken!
- [Tom] Where aren't you?
- [Joel] Is she gonna need a
ride out there or somethin'?
- [Crow] I don't know.
- [Tom] You're supposed
to walk to the revenge.
- I know you've heard
of the Star Kararu.
It's in the center of the
seventh constellation.
- Inhabited by a strong
and independent nation.
- [Joel] The Cherokee Nation.
- We have been aligned
with Kararu for centuries.
And now they are threatened.
Their mortal enemies have
developed a super weapon.
- Super weapon?
- [Crow] Well, a
really good one anyway.
- I don't have all the
details but we have
an intelligence report.
Apparently this weapon can
destroy a whole continent.
If we do nothing to prevent
it than I'm afraid Kararu
is doomed to extinction.
And that is the reason that
they got in touch with us.
- [Tom] Now we're alone.
- After giving it
careful consideration,
I've decided that you
are the only man capable
of doing the job.
- [Tom] So we're going
to get you a new dickey.
- But they've always
handled their own defenses.
- This time they've got
more than one enemy.
- [Tom] Pool table.
- It looks like the Valna
Raiders are going to attack.
Valnastar is one of
the strongest forces
of evil in our universe.
- [Crow] See, what'd I tell you?
(booming)
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] What gives?
- [Tom] Flashback, I don't know.
- [Crow] It's cool anyway.
- [Joel] Huh, I'm sorry,
I was just playin'
a video game in my head.
- I understand.
There's no way that they
can handle this alone.
- [Man Of Left] Yes, the
Kararuns are a valiant people
but they are no match
for the Valna Raiders.
- [Tom] Huh what, you
were talkin' to me?
Oh, I'm sorry, I was
thinking of the eighth hole
at Torrey Pines, sorry.
- [Joel] Let's cut
the crap, I love you.
- Very well.
I accept the mission.
- Good, excellent, I knew
you wouldn't disappoint us.
- [Joel] Yuck.
- [Man] I always look
forward to the crew check,
especially with such
a fine crew as the one
on the Bacchus-3.
- [Tom] I love it.
- [Joe] That's Rocky.
- [Tom] The flying squirrel.
- [Joe] The best space
pilot in the business.
- [Joel] And a good friend.
- [Joe] You remember
Dan, my navigator.
- [Ken] Indeed I do.
(laughs)
Oh, and this little darling
is your morale officer no doubt.
- [Man] Negative, sir.
The Lieutenant knows more
than the two us put together.
- [Ken] You don't say.
- Doesn't sound half bad.
- Young Billy,
he's going to make a
fine officer some day.
- It's a good crew, Joe.
- Not quite finished, sir.
- [Crow] Now I've got some
shots of the picnic here.
- Who's the busboy?
- A new face.
He looks like he could
handle himself in a fight.
- [Joe] Oh, he's rough
and ready all right.
But that's just what I
need on this mission.
- A real bruiser.
- [Joe] After all,
the Valna Raiders--
- [Tom] Send him to my room.
- Listen Joe, we're
asking you to set out
on a dangerous assignment.
We can't afford any unknown
quantities out there.
Do you know anything about
this man's background?
- I just wanna recruit this guy.
- [Crow] In the worst way.
- I wasn't planning
to adopt him.
- Joe, I like you.
- [Crow] But you're weird.
- Okay, if you think he's all
right than he's all yours.
- [Tom] Whoa, I'm in
China, I'm in China.
Oh no, it's just the...
- [Joel] Red ball jets help
you run faster, jump higher.
- [Tom] Cool.
Oh, I thought I was in
a Nestea commercial.
- [Crow] Oh, I see a bunny
and a cloud and a blonde wig
and a satin tap pant.
(gentle music)
- [Tom] Matching camisole.
- [Crow] If you do it right.
- [Tom] Another royalty check
for Herb Alpert coming up.
- [Joel] Some calf
muscles there.
I want your wig now!
- [Crow] It's been 26 miles.
It's only fun if I
catch you, wait up!
♪ It's a tangled storm of love ♪
- [Joel] Come on, it's my
turn to wear the night gown.
- [Tom] We gotta go folks.
- [Crow] Let's run.
- Rita.
Try to understand,
I did what I had to.
(lively music)
- Okay, now Crow, I
want you to be Ken.
And Tom I want you to be Ken.
- Joel, I feel ridiculous.
I'm dressed like Evel
Knievel only not so tasteful.
- Yeah Joel, I don't
wanna cast aspersions
on your little play-acting idea.
I don't wanna be the dead
squirrel under the floorboards
of your huntin' shack.
But this is the stupidest thing
you've ever had us do yet!
- Yeah Joe, you been
nippin' at the tester's glue
or what here?
- Come on, I just thought
it would be fun to play
the handsome captain
of the spaceship, okay?
It's a lark, a spoon,
run with me on this one.
I promise I'll never
make you do it again.
- Yeah, right.
Well, give it a week
I'll have a six-foot foam
scorpion stinger
hanging off my butt.
- Come on.
- Look, let's just get
this over with, okay?
- Just come on you
guys, it'll be a gas.
Okay, Cambot help
me out on this one.
Neutral drive off,
engines to full.
- All right, Ken.
- Now, cigar, Ken?
- Yuck.
- You know, no sense in
me returning back home.
What with my wife
and child gone.
- Oh, that's right, they took
a laser bolt, didn't they?
Too bad.
- You know, cigar Ken?
You know, a young fellow?
I could use a few
of 'em on my ship.
A young fella could do a
lot worse than throw in
with the lot of Bacchus-3.
We might even become friends.
- I don't understand, what
did I do to deserve this?
- We don't deserve
half the things we get.
(laughs)
You're stuck here!
- Gee, Joel, don't
vapor lock on us.
It's just a little skit
for cryin' out loud.
- Well, so I brought
the engines to neutral.
- Yeah, you do exactly as I
say and maybe you'll find out
what it means to be a
real man rather than just
a Wolf Raider.
- Yeah right, and you've
got a good chance to end up
at the Francis Farmer Motel.
(grunting)
- Jeez Joel, get a
hold of yourself!
- Nobody hits one
of my officers!
(alarms buzzing)
Oh no, the movie's starting, oh.
- [Tom] I think
you broke my jaw.
- [Joel] Sorry 'bout that.
- [Tom] Jeez, you're
outta control.
- [Crow] How symbolic.
- Are you on surveillance duty?
- Sorry I scared you.
You looked so angry I was afraid
I was gonna get strangled.
- [Tom] Well, there's
still time for that.
- Who's Rita, your wife
or your girlfriend?
- [All] Yes.
- Cat got your tongue?
- [Crow] Meow.
- Shut up!
Sorry, I'm just a little tired.
- You know Ken, I'm
beginning to think
you're not an earthling.
You haven't got the slightest
idea how to talk to a girl.
Honestly, I just
wanted to say hello.
You didn't have to
bite my head off.
- [Joel] Is that what I do?
- I don't feel like talking.
And I don't like people
meddling in my affairs.
- Oh, you don't?
Well have it your way.
- [Joel] At Burger King?
- [Narrator] This crew
had better start learning
to get along, it's gonna
be a difficult mission.
- [Joe] Our next mission
will take us to the Holy.
In the 32nd constellation
- [Tom] Holly Holy.
- However, before reaching
our final destination.
- [Joel] We all
get hats, big ones.
- [Tom] And scrambled eggs.
- Our assistance.
As you may have heard, Kararu
and Baholee are at war.
And recently the Wolf
Raiders have joined
forces with Baholee.
In other words,
this'll be no picnic.
- [Tom] More like a
small dinner party.
- Well, whatta
say, do we accept?
- [Tom] A buffet.
- Sir, I'd rather go and
fight than sit down here
bored out of my mind.
- Captain, I think this is
one mission where you're not
gonna need whiskey
for excitement.
(characters laughing)
- I'll need a stiff belt
when I get back though.
- [Crow] Ha, you'll
need a big belt.
- [Tom] I've got
baloney for arms!
- We're not gonna
take him along.
- [Joe] Cool it, Danny.
- But Captain, who is he?
- I've made my decision.
- What do we know about him?
- You can take it or leave it.
- [Tom] Well...
- Captain, I'm sorry, I'm sure
you know what you're doing.
- Captain, we accept
your decision.
Ken, welcome aboard.
- Are you sure you've got
what it takes for the job?
- You bet we have.
- [Tom] Don't press your luck.
- With Captain Joe in charge,
no mission is impossible.
- [Joe] Well, time will tell.
- [Crow] Monty
Python's Flying Circus.
- [Joel] Hey the crew got
free tanning sessions.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Pipe down,
pipe down please.
- [Joel] Pipe down please.
- [Tom] Pipe down please.
- All the way down here.
- [Crow] Now bite me please.
- [Joel] Hey.
(lively music)
- [Joel] What?
It's a good spaceship
in the cosmos.
- [Tom] What are Ma
and Pa Kettle goin'
on this mission or somethin'?
- [Crow] Hey there's Don Knotts.
(Joel laughing)
- [Joe] I've had her
rebuilt from stem to stern.
- [Tom] Neat huh?
- [Joe] To withstand the
extreme velocities out there.
I don't wanna have
another encounter
like I had with
the Wolf Raiders.
- [Rocky] I thought I was
gonna explode like a balloon.
- [Crow] Shouldn't have
had those buffalo wings.
- [Rocky] I sure hope
I never have to do
anything like that
again, Captain.
- [Billy] What are the
specs on this job, sir?
- [Joel] Oh, those are
bugs, they'll wash off.
- We've added a power
unit that can take us
up to speeds of
Mach 56 and over.
- [Crow] Yeah, pretty much.
- Any more speed
would tear us apart.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- You know.
- [Joel] Security guard?
- I'm really looking forward
to flying this old devil.
- So am I.
- Joe.
- Hi, Harry.
- [Tom] Hi teen gang.
- You really gonna
take on that mission?
- Sure thing.
- You leave the milk runs to us.
You always were a daredevil.
(chuckling)
By the way, is there
any truth to that rumor?
They say Rocky wants
out of this mission.
- [Tom] Come again?
- If he feels like a change,
I could sure use him.
- Sounds like someone's
overactive imagination.
Rocky's accounted
for, I wouldn't go
anywhere without him.
- Right on.
- [Crow] (laughs) You salty dog.
- Good luck.
- [Ken] This is a
strange development.
- [Tom] Wheels everywhere.
- [Ken] Using my superior
strength to fight my own people.
- [Crow] What is this,
The Wonder Years?
- [Ken] Sure I'd love
to liberate Valnastar
from the tyrant Halkun.
(imitating air hissing)
- [Tom] Lettin' the
air out of the tire.
- [Ken] My family's
up there and Rita.
Does she know I
killed her brother?
- [Joel] Maybe.
- [Ken] Will I ever be
able to explain to her
what really happened.
- [Tom] And what about
Naomi, will she love again?
- [Announcer] Is kindly
requested to report--
- [Joel] Trains, neat.
- [Tom] Cool, big ones.
- [Crow] Screamers.
- [Ken] That guy Rocky hates me.
Can Captain Joe control him?
- [Tom] Or not?
- [Crow] Will Joe admit
that Sue loves Mary?
(engine growling)
- [Joel] "Killdozer!"
with Clint Walker, no!
- Oh wow!
- Oh, oh no!
- [Crow] Eat fork, buddy.
- [Tom] He thinks I'm a palette.
- [Crow] Yeah well,
fortunate for me
I ate some more spinach
before I left the house.
- [Joel] Hey, come on, dim
your brights, I can't see!
(Tom grunting)
- [Tom] Oh, you should
know by now pal.
When you push a Wolf
Raider he pushes back.
(Tom chuckling)
(Tom grunting)
- [Crow] This must be one
of those Russian forklifts
I've heard so much about lately.
♪ This is the song written
for the train chase ♪
♪ This is chase Rocky and Ken ♪
♪ He tried to kill
me with a forklift ♪
♪ Ole ♪
- [Tom] Joe Mannix!
(singing)
- Rocky?
- [Crow] Again.
- Well that answers my question.
- [Tom] What was the question?
- I thought you
were a Wolf Raider.
They planted you on our flight
to sabotage our mission.
- [Joel] Yeah well,
you're a wuss raider.
(viewers giggling)
What are you doing,
are you high?
I have the strength of 20 men.
♪ This is the song right
after the train chase ♪
♪ This is the fight
Rocky and Ken ♪
- [Crow] Again?
- What's going on?
- [Joel] Nothing, sir.
- [Rocky] Captain!
- [Crow] Hazing the freshman.
- [Tom] I told you, no
grab-ass in the shower.
- I know who he is now.
- [Crow] He's my
mother, he's my sister.
He's my mother and my sister.
♪ He tried to kill
me with a forklift ♪
- Rocky, how often do
I have to tell you,
you should stop reading
those science fiction novels?
- [Crow] They're comic books.
- But captain?
- I know Ken's a lot
stronger than we are.
There's a reasonable scientific
explanation for that.
He spent a lot of time
in another constellation.
That increases strength.
- [Joel] You are a
liar, I don't believe,
you're just like him.
- [Ken] Don't expect
any gratitude from me.
- [Tom] Okay.
- I won't.
Now you listen to this.
- [Crow] Pull my finger.
- What I expect from
you is total obedience.
- [Tom] If that's okay with you.
- You know you'll
only continue to live
as long as I shut up.
(dramatic music)
♪ I got a threat
from the captain ♪
- [Joel] Shut up.
- [Crow] Wow.
- [Tom] Amazing!
Ooh, ah!
Ooh, gah, it's so great.
- [Crow] It's only a model.
- [Tom] All right, spit
out the sunflower seeds.
- [Narrator] And so, our
valiant space adventurers
prepared to embark on a
perilous and exciting mission.
- [Joel] Hold the
ship, lose the building
with Jerry Lewis, Charlie
Kalkenski, Franking!
(Tom humming tune)
- [Narrator] Meanwhile,
on Valnastar.
- [Tom] Say.
- [Announcer] Other
plans are being made.
- [Halkun] Remember
Rita, it is our law.
You may not return until--
- [Joel] Brian Jones?
- [Tom] Tell me spirit,
are these shadows
of things which must
be or which might be?
(birds chirping)
(Tom mumbling)
- [Tom] Hey look, 27 eight
by 10 colored glossy pictures
with the circles and
arrows and the paragraph
on the back of each one.
- [Crow] Why am I thinking
of the cast party now?
Oh, I like that one.
- Maryanne.
- [Joel] Uh, that'll be
53 bucks for the photos.
- Barbara.
- [Tom] Whose hand is that?
- [Crow] I can be Barbara.
- My baby, my wife.
- [Crow] Whatever.
- I don't care anymore
what happens to me
out beyond the stars.
- Ooh.
- If I don't survive, then
we can be together again
that much sooner.
- [Joel] Oh, would somebody
turn the fryer light off me.
- I miss you so.
Rest peacefully until
then, it won't be long now.
- [Tom] What a sap.
(soft music)
- [Joel] What, oh, I've got
the wrong grave, I'm sorry.
- [Crow] Olga, that is, whoops.
- [Tom] Oh, it's embarrassing.
- [Joel] I gotta go
paint a house now, sorry.
- Well, that just
about sums it all.
- [Crow] Hey they're
havin' a jumpsuit party
and his is the grandest of all.
- Thanks, you're a great crew.
- [Joel] Ready to
levitate the table?
- To the mission.
- [Crew] Cheers!
- [Tammy] Rocky, aren't
you going to drink with us?
- [Tom] Gonna fly now?
- Sir, I want you--
- [Joel] In the worst way.
- To order me to
go on this mission.
- I sure will.
Rocky, I order you
to pilot Bacchus-3.
- Yes, sir.
I guess you're stuck
with me at the controls.
Let's go for it then.
- You old space hound.
- [Crow] (laughs) You
pile of space crap.
- This is yours.
- [Tom] It has your
initials on it.
I made it in shop
class just for you.
♪ This is the song
on the space mod ♪
♪ We'll drink to
the brotherhood of ♪
(beeping)
- Hello?
- [Tom] You're not
gonna drink that!
- Yes, Captain, it's for you.
- [Joel] Fisher
Price phone, sir.
- Oh, hello?
- [Tom] What about my
cheeks you, I, whoa.
- Departure.
- [Crow] Wait, they're
having cocktails.
- Nine, eight, seven.
- [Joel] Mouseketeers sign in.
- [Tom] Cubby!
- [Announcer] Five, four.
- [Crow] Roy!
- [Tom] Jimmy!
Annette!
- [Crow] Chad.
- [Announcer] Zero.
- [Joel] Looks like it's
anything can happen day, sir.
- [Announcer] Lift off!
- [Tom] Remember that the
Mouseketeers and Mickey Mouse
are registered trademarks
of Disney Incorporated,
Buena Vista Television,
Touchstone Pictures.
Any the unlicensed distribution
of any of these images
that are not remotely resembling
any Walt Disney images
is expressly forbidden
by Disney, Buena Vista,
Touchstone and Michael Eisner.
- [Crow] Hey watch
out for the tower.
- Look out, oh!
- [Narrator] Bacchus-3
blasted off for her next
encounter with destiny.
This mission would be the
most demanding the ship
and her crew had ever
been asked to endure.
- [Tom] But first, this message.
- [Crow] Presser, cabin presser,
like an Arab, they write.
- [Announcer] Captain
Joe immediately tested
the newly installed speed
acceleration equipment.
- [Crow] Duck boy.
(Crow quacking)
- [Narrator] And he
had to know early on
if the crew could
take the pressure.
- [Joel] I can't, my
face goes all funny sir.
- [Crow] That's quite a
tic you got there, son.
- [Tom] Let's loosen up
with some butter gutters.
- [All] Butter gutter,
butter gutter, butter gutter
butter gutter, butter gutter.
- [Joel] I can't stop, I
don't know how it works.
Good-bye, folks.
- [Tom] Good-bye, good-bye.
- [Joel] Tibet International.
- [Crow] The white zone is for
loading and unloading only.
(Tom grunting)
- [Tom] Ooh!
- [Joe] Engine, off.
- [Rocky] Engine off.
- [Tom] Engine off.
- Doesn't it feel great to
be back on the ground again?
(chuckling)
- [Tom] Oh, a trouser
cam, hi there.
- They sent someone to meet us.
Ken, release the gangway.
- [Tom] Call me Ken.
- [Crow] Okay, Ken.
Nice gangway.
- [Tom] Is that the gangway?
- [Crow] How much
does a gang weigh?
- [Joel] (imitates
beeping) Welcome back.
- [Tom] Oh no, it's
the plant of Tweakies.
- [Crow] Oh boy.
- [Tom] What a nightmare.
- [Crow] What could be worse?
It's a planet of Gallaghers.
- [Tom] That's worse.
- [Crow] Melon crazy.
- That's worse.
- No!
- Captain Joe.
- [Tom] Movin' kinda slow.
- He seems to know you.
- Captain Joe and one
officer, follow me.
- [Joe] Yes, sir.
- The rest wait here 'til
you receive further orders.
- Doesn't sound too friendly.
- [Joe] Can it, Rocky.
- [Joel] Again, canning it, sir.
- I'm going to
establish contact.
Meanwhile you wait here.
- [Joel] Good idea.
- [Joe] Let's keep it cool.
We're gonna be involved in
very delicate negotiations.
- [Crow] There's cold cuts in
the fridge and some Armor All
in the glovebox, and keep
out of the liquor cabinet.
- [Tom] Good-bye, see you later.
- [Joel] Get him teen gang!
- [Dan] Get Back!
(grunting)
I'm taking in the gangway.
- [Joel] And I'm taking
in my little pants.
- Has anybody here
got a deck of cards?
- They're supposed
to be our allies.
I was never welcomed
anywhere like this before.
- [Tom] Somewhere in
the Black Mountain Hills
out in the middle of
some alien planet.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Think I look stupid,
you should see my boss.
- [Joel] Hey this is
nice, comfortable.
Nice ride.
(imitates engine)
Neat, wow.
Oh, now they're big
and they're in Mexico.
- [Tom] You guys wait here,
I gotta go cash a check.
Tap a kidney.
Nice digs.
(Crow humming)
- [Crow] Welcome to the
dance of incontinence.
- [Tom] Huh?
- [Crow] I mean
seven continents.
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Crow] It's kind of a--
- [Tom] Heh, bathroom.
- [Joel] Why are there
garage doors all of a sudden?
- [Tom] Easy access?
- [All] Say, hello.
- [Ken] What is this
strange feeling inside me?
- [Joel] It's a
voiceover called love.
- There's people
out there somewhere
and I wanna be part of it.
Yes, sir.
- [Crow] That's my baby.
- Well, I think I'll do
a little reconnaissance.
- [Crow] See a
man about a horse.
- We were ordered to stay
here, You can't leave the ship.
Ken!
- [Crow] Ken, go after Ken.
- Hey Billy, let's
join him out there.
- Right.
- [Tammy] Stop or I'll shoot!
- [Billy] Hey!
- [Joel] Everybody
run, Tammy's got a gun.
- We have orders to wait
here in this spacecraft.
And that's exactly
what we're going to do.
- [Tom] She is
management material.
- We have to stick together.
- [Crow] Aw come one guys, now
I wanna do what I wanna do.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Imperial
Margarine presents.
Kenquistador.
♪ Kenquistador ♪
♪ He tried to kill
me with a forklift ♪
♪ That's Ken ole ♪
- [Ken] When I was fighting
with the Wolf Raiders.
- [Crow] Step on a crack,
break your mother's back.
- [Joel] Break your own back.
- [Tom] Your mother
was a saint by the way.
(cheering)
- [Tom] Top of the world, Ma.
(laughing)
- Yippee!
- [Crow] Looks like he got
his prescription filled.
- [Ken] Bang, bang, bang.
- [Crow] And he's
revertin' to childhood.
- [Joel] I'm sorry about Ken.
They've had a hard with
him adjusting to school.
They say he's gifted though.
- [Tom] More tea, no
thanks I've had eight cups.
- Say, how much longer now?
- His excellency will
be with you shortly.
- I believe you said
that two hours ago.
- [Crow] I don't need this crap.
(snoring)
- [Tom] New from Chun King.
- [Crow] Oh great, a floor show.
- [Tom] Ooh, is the great TE
Lawrence going to join us now?
- [Joel] Ah, we don't
know if we should stand
'cause we don't know if
you're a man or a woman yet.
- I'm Captain Joe.
This is Rocky, my first officer.
- Ordainja, Lord of Kararu.
- [Crow] It's Dorff.
He's a guy, we can sit down.
- [Tom] I'm a
gaudy son of a gun.
- [Man] We asked you
to leave your planet
and come and help us
because of hostilities
with the Star Caesar.
- [All] Romero.
- I don't understand, why
have they declared war on you?
- They want what we have.
We have mineral resources
Caesar is envious of.
Rather than pay for
them like everyone else,
they think they can obtain
them by force and violence.
- We used to laugh at Caesar.
Unfortunately they've
grown stronger.
Dangerously stronger.
- [Ordainja] They've
acquired a super weapon
which could destroy our planet.
Or possibly our
whole constellation.
(festive music playing)
- [Crow] Hey, sounds like
Jack Benny playing a violin.
(background chattering)
- [Tom] Indy, my friend Indy.
(background chattering
in foreign language)
- [Joel] Trumpy, you're stinky.
- [Tom] Skin mittens.
- [Crow] Now Ken honey,
don't touch anything
and stay close to Mom.
- [Tom] I'll just blend
in with the crowd here.
(Tom humming)
- [Joel] A nun's habit for me?
No thanks but you're sweet.
- [Crow] I love the Ren Fest.
- [Tom] Oh, they must have
had a close-out on taffeta.
Look at those guys.
(background chattering)
Kids.
I was one once.
Oh, what's this?
Looks like I made a little
somethin' in the deal.
It's so fun.
- [Joel] This give me an idea.
- Hi.
- [Tom] How you
doin, see you later.
- [Crow] Must be Mardi Gras.
- [Joel] Carnival.
- Hey, a bar!
- [Crow] Hey Chris Walken's
playin' Russian roulette.
- [Joel] Totally new
concept, it's a church bar.
(background chattering)
- Hello.
- [Crow] Say Brandy,
fetch another round.
- [Tom] She serves
them whiskey and wine.
This Midori is really good.
- Boy, I don't like your face.
- [Joel] Eh, I'm not
a big fan either sir.
- Get lost.
- [Crow] You gotta
nice personality.
- [Patron] I guess
you're not from here.
Otherwise you'd know
it's good manners
to drink with friends, here.
- [Tom] I'd rather share a
needle with Keith Richards.
- I told you to drink!
- [Joel] Aw, Mom's
gonna smell this on me.
- [Ken] Doesn't he know I
can kill him with one blow?
- [Tom] Some ego, buddy.
- [Patron] Strangers
aren't welcome.
- [Crow] Gonna be a fight.
Fight, okay.
- Bye.
- [Patron] Hey,
where are you goin'?
- [Tom] Ooh, to
get a Band-Aid, ow!
My nose.
- [Patron] This will teach ya!
- [Crow] That's the problem
with private school.
- [Tom] Yeah,
yeah, you get this.
- [Joel] Ugh, thank you
sir, may I have another?
- [Tom] I like you guys.
- Here's one more.
- [Joel] Well, looks like
we've got three separate views
of Love, American Style.
- [Crow] Get up, get
up, get up, crunch,
Bam!
- [Tom] Buck!
- [Joel] Biff!
- [Crow] Bappy!
Eh, no.
♪ Lay down the boogie and
play that funky music ♪
♪ Till you die ♪
- [Tom] Next on Taxi,
or Barney Miller.
One of the two.
- [Joel] What?
Oh, he killed him
with a curling iron.
Goodness.
- You're just...
- [Crow] A gigolo.
- Get him!
(gun fire ricocheting)
- [Joel] Yeah, get him, it's
his turn to buy the pitcher!
- [Patron] Stop him! (groaning)
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Oh, he
stumbled back into
the Renaissance
Festival, huzzah.
♪ There's a place on Mars
where the women smoke cigars ♪
- [Joel] He looked in my
bag, I'll have to kill him.
- [Tom] Marian.
Oh, suddenly it is Ishtar here.
- In here!
- [Crow] Hey that's
a dressing room.
- Where is he?
- I saw him go in there.
- Come on!
- [Tom] Indy!
- [Joel] Oh, it's
a woman's restroom.
We can't go in there.
(mimicking snoring)
- [Joel] This is getting
ridiculous, you know?
- [Tom] Sir I think
you're losing them.
Tell a joke, juggle
or something.
- Just a second,
I'll be right back.
- [Joel] God, did you
say something to him
while I was
sleeping, what gives?
- [Crow] Hey look, it's
the all can network.
(dramatic music)
- Look who's in trouble.
What did he do?
- [Tom] Killed a man just
for snorin' too loud.
- [Crow] Who's ready
for pudding, huh?
- Was in the space craft
during our negotiations.
That man was arrested in a
storehouse for precious stones.
- [Tom] Arrested?
- What was he doing in there?
- [Joe] Your excellency,
if he left the ship
it was in direct
violation of my orders.
- You ordered him
to steal the stones.
- [Tom] Oh, thanks
for spitting on us.
- [Joel] This guy's a king?
- I'm afraid he doesn't
take orders seriously.
- I ordered him to stay aboard.
- Then you don't mind
if I cut off his head?
- [Crow] No, that's
why we brought him.
- Not at all, suit yourself.
- [Joel] I tire of pudding.
Bring me something salty,
and crunchy, and sweet.
- Order the execution.
Where were we?
- [Crow] Goofy land.
- We were discussing the fee.
- That's right.
- [Tom] Ah, yes.
- Let me give you
your down payment.
- [Tom] My little bag.
- One.
- [Tom] Little.
- Two.
- Three.
- [Tom] Little Indians,
I love that one.
- Three!
(laughing)
- [Tom] It's Jimmy Cow Black,
the Indian in the group.
- [Joel] Milk from
the mother stone.
Snot's block?
- We'll collect the
rest on completion.
- [Crow] Of the Brooklyn Bridge?
- [Tom] Hey, Sonny
Rollins is out there.
- [Joel] Hey, my helmet's
chafing, Steve, you?
- [Crow] Igor,
quit playing that.
(tense music)
- [Tom] Sure is quiet.
Too quiet.
- [Crow] That oboe's
comin' from that room.
- [Tom] It's the Rite
of Spring, Stravinsky?
They let him have a
chamber group in his cell?
- [Crow] No, a chamber pot.
- [Tom] Oh.
Musical pot.
- [Joel] Thanks for the
little prelude, guys.
I've got a crazy Star Wolf
idea that just might work.
(grunting)
- [Crow] His Mickey Mouse gloves
give him incredible power.
- [Tom] That's a
trademark of whatever.
(metal clanging)
Huh?
Hmm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
- [Joel] Spider-Man.
- [Crow] Yeah but not
the new Spider-Man,
the old Spider-Man when he had
the good costume and when--
- [Tom] Ssh.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Huh?
- [Crow] Oh great, first
day on the job I lose a guy.
Ah?
- Come on, get down!
This is no monkey cage.
- [Joel] This is no disco,
this ain't no fooling around.
(Ken laughing)
- I was just checking
out the layout here.
- [Joel] The cool
moldings, you have a couple
cobwebs and stuff.
- I can't find the exit.
If I can't find
one, I'll make one.
- Cut the funny stuff.
You've just been
ordered executed.
That oughta take the
smile off your face.
- [Crow] Not if you do it right.
- By the way, don't
waste your energy.
You can't get outta here.
No earthling can.
- Earthling?
- Not even a Wolf Raider
could break out of this place.
- Is that so?
We'll see about that!
- [Tom] Meanwhile
back at the cool ship.
- Captain, anyone
can make a mistake.
Just as long as you don't
keep on repeating it.
I think we should
get rid of Ken.
- [Tom] Which one?
- I disagree.
Have you already forgotten?
Ken saved our lives, I think
he deserves another chance.
Don't you agree?
- Okay.
- [Tom] Man of firm conviction.
- I guess you're right.
I'll take him back
on one condition.
- [Joel] You stop drinking
and start going to meetings.
- There's a Caesar
officer in that jail.
- Mm.
- [Tom] Mm.
- You think Ken can help
him break out of there.
- Let's go to it.
Establish contact with Ken's
secret radio, on the double!
- [Crow] No you guys go ahead.
I'm sick, I'll just stay
here and not go through that.
- [Tom] I wish I
had a harmonica.
(beeping)
- Hmm?
- [Crow] Cleveland
you're on the air.
- [Joe] Ken, can you hear me?
It's me, Joe.
- [Joel] Yeah, I
really miss you, dude.
We haven't talked
since high school.
What's goin' on?
- You never told me about
this cute little gadget.
- [Joe] You don't have
to know everything.
- [Tom] What's romance
without a little surprise?
- [Joe] We wanted to
wanted to make sure
you wouldn't double-cross us.
- And I guess I passed your
examination, haven't I?
Now what do you want me to do?
- [Joe] Listen carefully.
- [Tom] Turn your
head and cough.
- Ken, there's a Caesar
officer in your jail.
We need him as camouflage
when we move onto Caesar.
They won't suspect
anything if we show up
with one of their officers.
We want you to
contact that officer.
Get him and yourself
out of prison.
- Why don't you just ask
the Kararun authorities
to release us?
- [Crow] Well, if you're so
smart why are you in jail?
- [Joe] Five minutes
and they got suspicious.
If I say I wanna
take him to Caesar,
chances are they'll
think I joined forces
with their mortal enemies.
- Are you sure I can
find him and get him
out of this prison?
- [Joe] Sure Ken, I
have complete confidence
you can bring it off.
- Ssh, somebody coming.
- [Joel] 'Course I'm drunk.
- [Tom] And I'm sure
the other inmates
haven't heard a word of this.
(mimicking snoring)
♪ Hmm hmm hmm we're
just sleeping ♪
(Joel chuckling)
- [Joel] Works every time.
- He's gone now.
Listen sir, aren't the
Kararuns likely to suspect you
if I break out of here?
- The Kararuns can
suspect anything they want
as long as I can
get off this planet.
- [Crow] And he's got
the generous cheeks.
- I understand.
Only, how am I supposed to
get out of this prison cell?
Those bars are as
strong as tree trunks.
- [Tom] Here's how I escape.
- Is Star Wolf
suddenly going soft?
- Just give me my orders.
- [Tom] Soft wolf.
- You'll find you've got some
clever little items with you.
- Go on.
- Okay, I want you
to listen carefully.
- [Joel] All right, I'm
using a split screen.
Can you see me now?
- [Crow] It's the
Patty Duke show.
- Now take a good look at your
far right shoulder button.
- [Tom] Oh, make you look!
- Equipped it with a
miniature nuclear device.
- [Joel] Shouldn't
I have known that?
- Works a little like a grenade.
- [Tom] Neat.
- Whatever you wanna
blow up, attach it to it.
- Are any more of
these buttons grenades?
- Check your lapel.
Now you see how
much I trust you?
- [Tom] That's genuine
mother of pearl there.
- Thanks, now then, what
happens if I don't find
this Caesar officer?
- [Crow] Ah, we
blow your neck off.
- You will because you have to.
- [Crow] Let's blow
ours, away, yay!
- Abandoning you here.
- Look, don't you think this
is an awfully tall order?
- Ken, I know you can handle it.
- Joel, doggonit, this
film has me bamboozled.
- Yeah, think about it.
We've got this guy who used
to wear a wig but doesn't
any more whose joined
up with Captain Gerbil
and the leatherette squad.
And everybody's having more
flashbacks than Bruce Dern
in "The Trip".
- Yeah and now he's
held captive by Don Ho
and a kid who drinks Tranya,
and who's fightin' who and why?
- And why are all these alien
transvestites attacking earth
anyway and what about this
Japanese preoccupation
with the name Ken?
- Okay, okay you
guys, take it easy.
I knew you were gonna have
a problem with this movie
but that's what
I'm here for, okay?
The real problem with this
film is it's not really
a movie at all.
It's just a bunch of Japanese
TV shows strung together
to look like a movie, so
that's what's going on.
- So it's like Bergman's
"Scenes from a Marriage" then?
- Exact, huh?
- Oh, or Schwarz's "A
Very Brady Christmas".
- Just listen up you two, you
just might learn something.
This is the screenplay
model developed by Syd Field
in his runaway bestseller
book "Screenplay".
Here's how it works,
Cambot help me out here.
The first act establishes
setting and the major characters
we'll get to know.
And then the first plot point
comes along and sends it all
zigging everywhere and then
into another direction!
So can anybody give me an
example of what that would be
in today's movie?
- Ah, the credits.
- No Crow, come on.
- Oh, I know, it's when Mephisto
and the blonde chick with the...
Oh, I'm just grabbing
at straws here, Joel.
- No everybody, it's
when Ken joins Star Force
and goes up against
his old allies.
- Which Ken?
- Oh, the one with
the wig, right?
- Right, now in act two, we
reveal the conflict in the film.
Does anybody know what that is?
- Take a leap, Crow.
- Oh, let's see, it's
either the credits or, well
it's when Ken, in the wig,
fights his own inner struggle
which is punctuated with
his conflict with the other
crew members and his shaky
alliance with Captain Cheeky
who drinks a lot, by the way,
and oh, that's the subplot!
- That's very good, Crow,
okay, that's act two.
Now given these
pieces of the puzzle,
does anybody know how plot
point two will turn out?
- Oh, oh, oh, that's easy.
Scout sees Atticus Finch
shoot the dog in the street
which shows that he
has the capacity...
Oh no, that's "To
Kill a Mockingbird".
- Oh, right, I'll
jump in here, okay.
Let's just imagine that the
blonde assassin comes in,
and shows her love for Ken,
her undying love for Ken
and instead of
serving two masters,
they die in a
harakiri love pact.
- No come on, Joel, this is
Sandy Frank, not Kurosawa.
- My guess is that it goes
on like the mess it is
with no resolution and
we're all left feeling empty
and unfulfilled like
Fassbinder's tragic hero
in "Berlin Alexanderplatz".
- You my friend, get a RAM chip.
- Ha!
- All right, what
do you think, sirs?
- Well, William Gold
Joel, we have a theory.
- You know, Toni Morrison
best known for her literary
tour de force "Beloved",
may well be one
of the fastest rising.
(clanging)
- Tie him up, Frank.
(upbeat music)
- Where do I--
- [Crow] Poor Jack Perkins, oi.
- Not back from the spaceship.
- Signal us when you're clear.
Over and out.
- [Tom] Shoulder phone off.
When I talk to Ken
I touch myself.
- [Ken] What's that?
- [Joel] Neat.
- I heard a noise.
- [Tom] That's you talking.
- Someone's coming.
- [Crow] Mm, horses,
12, 13 maybe.
- Coast is clear.
- [Joel] But the tide is out.
- [Crow] Open channel D.
- [Tom] Blooming ground flower.
Light then get away
with loud report.
Ooh!
- [Joel] (laughs) Like a
hot knife through butter.
- [Crow] Hi, diva.
- [Tom] Eat at Joe's, eat
at Joe's, eat at Joe's,
eat at Joe's, Eat at Joe's.
Merry Xmas, eat at Joe's.
- [Joel] Now this is a little
something just for moi.
- [Tom] I think Ken's makin'
a little too much out of this,
they're just Christmas
lights for cryin' out loud.
- [Crow] Somethin' to do.
- [Tom] Eh well.
♪ Oh the tone sets
the scene do dee do ♪
♪ Do do do ♪
Huh?
Coulda sworn I, mwah!
Kissing monster,
kissing monster.
- [Tom] Nice dive.
So much for those lights.
- [Crow] (laughs) Yeah.
- [Joel] These
looks like bars, hm.
- [Tom] Hm.
Hm?
It's a busboy.
- [Crow] Hey, can
you clear my table?
- Hey.
Hey!
- [Joel] It's Ho, not Hey, a
lot of people get confused.
- Are you the Caesar officer?
- [Tom] I've heard
so much about you.
- Yes.
- [Tom] Do you like me,
do you find me pleasing?
- And I gather
you're the earthling
who was captured earlier today.
- [Joel] I've heard some
of them talk about lately.
- How did you get
out of your cell?
- Just a little good luck.
- You escaped.
- [Crow] No, I'm still
here, will you come on?
- Listen.
- [Tom] Do you want
to know a secret?
- [Ken] We've got
no time to lose.
- Okay.
- [Joel] Okay, do you want
some fries with that then, sir.
- [Tom] He's not a
Caesarian officer,
he's an Arby's trainee.
- The Kararuns must
have anesthetized me
before they put me in my cell.
I have no idea
where I am in here.
Can you guide me
if I get you out?
- Yes.
I've been locked up in
this miserable place
for the last two months.
- [Tom] Aw.
- On my way to the
courtyard for exercise,
I've memorized every corridor.
- That's great.
- [Crow] You look great.
- You're not afraid are
you, can I trust you?
- You can, just
get me out of here.
- I will.
Move away.
- [Crow] Someplace
nice, like the Hamptons.
- [Joel] See, it's
a tiny time pill.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] What manner of man
are you who can summon flame
without flint or tinder?
- [Joel] Some call me Ken.
- [Tom] Oh, it's neat,
you can buy these things
in North Dakota or Wisconsin.
I buy 'em by the
brick, by the gross.
They've got like
black cats and stuff.
- [Crow] Well some locks
are two bomb locks. (laughs)
I'll just try it again.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- Not like that, you
gotta put it on two bars.
- [Joel] Oh yeah,
suddenly you're
the explosive
button expert right?
♪ Ba ba ba ba ba ♪
- [Tom] Alexander
Solkin presents.
- [Crow] Stupid Boy.
- [Tom] In color.
- [Crow] Huzzah.
- [Tom] Alakazam.
- [Joel] Rubbermaid bars, neat.
- I've never seen anyone
as strong as you are.
- [Tom] Except Sheena Easton.
- Come on, let's
get out of here.
Where to?
- [Joel] To the top.
- [Tom] Hurray.
- There's only one way out.
Listen, the door's
locked on the outside.
- What's on the other side?
- Two Kararun guards.
- [Tom] Paradise.
- Heavily armed.
- Okay, here's what we do.
- [Crow] Hey, that's dirty!
(screaming)
♪ Ho dee ho I hurt myself. ♪
- [Ken] Open the door,
I've been hurt, open up.
Somebody help me.
- [Guard] What's going on?
- [Tom] Huh?
- [Joel] Uh-oh.
- [Joel] Oh, ah, kick,
punch, lunge, ha, oh!
- [Crow] I hurt myself.
- [Tom] What, hmm?
- Good work, let's go.
- [Joel] It's boots forever.
- [Tom] It's Bootsy Collins.
- [Joel] Oh.
- [Crow] You die, Joe!
(weapons firing)
(grunting)
- We'll have to fight it out.
- [Tom] Well what do
you think we're doing?
- [Crow] Next time I say
let's go to Boliva, let's go!
Not me, you idiot, no!
(grunting)
- [Crow] Fighting, elbow,
shooting, fighting, oh,
tumbling, killing,
dying over, oh, oh,
got over, punch through.
Ouch, ooh ooh.
- [Joel] It's okay, friend.
- [Tom] Oh, ouch, punch.
- [Crow] Oh, right in the back!
Oh that hurt, oh.
- [Tom] Breaking rhubarb.
- Come on, give me one of those.
- [Tom] No, not one of those.
- [Crow] Oh, thank you.
- You really picked
those two off easily.
- Well, I'm not a bad shot.
Watch this.
- [Tom] Oh, that
was a thrill kill.
(alarm beeping)
- [Crow] Duck alarm, run.
- [Joel] Oh, we got an
extra point on that.
(dramatic music)
- This way.
(upbeat music)
- [Officer] Water!
- Careful, it
might be an ambush.
- [Crow] Wait a minute, it
tastes salty, it's grey water!
(grunting)
- [Ken] Ah!
- [Tom] Delicious.
Huh?
- There they are.
(weapons firing)
- [Tom] Ooh.
Ah.
Terrible violence.
- [Joel] Terrible.
- [Tom] Oh, they're
only shooting flares.
- [Crow] I think
they're talcum bombs.
- [Tom] Yeah, could be.
Huh?
- [Joel] Die, Joel.
- [Tom] Huh?
- [Tom] Button bombs, whoa!
- [All] Ah!
- [Crow] Hey wow, those
things really work.
- [Joel] You gotta
remember to take them off
before you take your
clothes to the laundry.
- [Crow] Oh, yeah.
- [Tom] Blow up a dry cleaner.
Oh, this was a good
plan, wasn't it?
Whoops.
All right, come on
in, bring her down.
Little right, little right.
Up there you go, watch
your space cushion.
It's a little driving joke.
Bring it down, keep
going, come on, come on.
- [Crow] No, I'm sorry
you failed your test.
You'll have to come
back in two weeks.
Happens to most of the guys.
- This is Joe.
- [Joel] Hello Joe,
what do you know?
- [Tom] Just got
back from Kokomo.
(laughing)
- You surprised me
of your position.
Ken?
- [Tom] Ken?
- Can you hear me,
Ken, please come in.
(soft music)
- [Tom] Ready?
♪ I love Ken and a guy named
Ken and it hurts me so ♪
♪ I'm in love Ken and a guy
named Ken and it hurts me so ♪
♪ And it hurts me so ♪
- [Joel] Moses?
- [Ken] Arita.
- [Crow] Meter maid, where
would I be without you.
- I'm seeing things.
- [Joel] No, you're seeing me.
Is that what I am
to you, a thing?
- This must be a hallucination.
- [Crow] With that
hair it must be.
- Rita!
What are you doing here?
- I've been trying to
track you down for days.
We got a radio message
that you'd broken out
of a Kararu jail.
They said you were a traitor.
And here you are in an
Earth Space Command uniform.
- [Tom] Traiting.
- I was forced to
wear this uniform.
They said they'd
kill me otherwise.
- Mm hm.
- A likely story.
I don't know what's
come over you, Ken.
- [Crow] I want my tapes back.
- You've turned
traitor, abandoned me
and killed my brother.
- It was an accident.
- [Tom] Okay.
- He was getting ready
to shoot a little boy
whose name also
happened to be Ken.
I was just trying to stop him.
- [Woman] Ken!
- Mom!
- [Tom] But we'll
just run the clip.
- Don't shoot!
(groaning)
- [Crow] Oh, come on, we're
intimate with this scene
for crying out loud.
- Traitor.
- That's what really
happened, Rita.
I swear I'm telling
you the truth.
I'm not a traitor
to our country.
You know that, I simply refused
to kill an innocent child.
And I didn't want to
fight with your brother!
- [Joel] So I killed him.
- [Rita] I believe you.
You can't betray a country
you never belonged to.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- [Rita] Ken, you once told
me your father came to Valna
as a missionary.
- [Tom] Oh, that bag,
I thought they cleared
that up in counseling.
- [Rita] You're
really an earthling.
- Go on, go on, murder me in
cold blood if you want to.
- You deserve worse,
to die a slow death.
- Then what are you waiting for?
I know Valna law
as well as you do.
I caused your brother's
death and now you've been
sent out to kill me.
Well I'm all ready to die, Rita.
- Ken...
- You'd be doing me a favor,
I can't live in dishonor.
Go ahead, shoot!
- [Crow] But first,
swallow my lapel button
as a symbol of our love, hmm?
- [Tom] Shoot him
down, shoot to kill.
- [Joel] Stinker.
- [Tom] Buck fever.
Oh, it's made out of
electrician's tape,
for crying out loud.
- [Ken] Come on,
get it over with.
What's the point of
living if the girl I love
more than life itself
thinks that I'm a traitor?
- [Joel] Kill him.
- [Tom] Kill him.
- Now, Rita.
- [Tom] Now.
- [Crow] Hey, this is
just like Richard III.
- [Tom] Sure is.
(Rita sobbing)
Won't do it.
- [Joel] It took me seven
days to get this gun,
now I can't use it.
- [Ken] Rita!
- [Tom] Damn.
Nice to see there was a
dam in the background.
- [Joel] That peasant
blouse is all wrong on her.
- Rita.
- I can't do it, I can't
kill the man I love.
- [Crow] Then kill
the one you're with.
(Tom mimicking gunshot)
- Oh, my foot, why am I
having such a crappy day?
- Rita.
- [All] Meter maid.
- [Tom] There's that
glycerin tear again.
- My darling.
Ken.
- [Tom] I'm gonna have
to remember that line
for the bars, it works.
(sobbing)
- [Crow] You're
crying on my bomb.
- [Tom] Ooh.
Ouch.
- [Ken] Rita!
- [Joel] Oh, get off
the tilt-a-whirl.
- [Tom] Ooh, oh, it's over.
- [Crow] That was great.
- What happens to us now?
Are we both just
fugitives in space?
No matter what you
or I say or do,
they'll never let us go home.
Valna, I'd love to see it again.
- What do we need Valna
for, we've got each other.
We can start a new
life somewhere else.
- [Tom] On a slag heap?
- Rita, it won't work.
They'll never leave us
in peace, you know that.
- How can you say that?
If we keep loving each
other, we'll find a way.
- [Joel] Boy you are naive.
- How long can that love last?
You know what you'll see every
morning when you wake up?
You'll be staring
straight at the man
who killed your brother.
- [Crow] Will you be there too?
- Ken.
- It won't work, Rita, too much
has already happened to us.
Soon we'd start
hating each other.
- I won't let you
talk like that.
- It just won't work.
Why didn't you kill me before?
- Oh!
- What?
- You heard, kill me
and get it over with.
- [Tom] Come on chicken, you
chicken, come on kill me,
come on chicken.
(clucking)
- [Joel] I wonder
what he's thinking.
- [Crow] Ditch her, go run!
- [Tom] You are going to die.
I am going to kill you.
- Ken!
Ken!
- [Tom] Rita!
(soldier screaming)
(gasps)
He killed the tree.
(weapons firing)
(Ken groans)
- Rita!
- [All] Meter maid!
- Rita, are you all right?
- [Crow] I killed your
other brothers by the way.
- Ken.
Traitor.
It was you who fired that shot.
It was you.
- [Joel] Wait, let
me explain, oh, darn.
- [Ken] Rita!
The most important part
of me just died too.
- [Crow] Well, at
least he gets to keep
that swell Star Trek stuff.
- [Tom] Well honey, looks like
I'm gonna have to gut you.
- [Joel and Crow] Oh!
- [Joel] That's it, make
it look like a robbery.
- I heard gunfire.
Are you all right?
- [Crow] Where have you been?
- [Ken] I'm fine,
the others are dead.
- Who's she, what
happened to her?
- A Kararun girl got
caught in the crossfire.
- [Crow] Huh, bummer.
- It's late, we
better get going.
There's nothing we can do here.
- [Tom] But I'm thirsty again.
- [Crow] Will you get going?
- [Ken] Good-bye,
Rita, good-bye.
- [Joel] Come
back, I'm not dead.
You didn't check for a pulse.
(tense music)
- [Crow] Next time
on Twin Peaks.
- Help, Ken.
- I've got you.
- [Tom] Come 'ere you, come on.
- [Joel] Let him go, drop him.
- [Tom] Would you take those
rocks out of your pockets?
- [Crow] Rock climbing, Joel.
- [Tom] Rock climbing.
- [Crow] Caesar Romero?
Edmund Hillary?
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Oh, they're
down there, jump for it!
- Hey, hey, hey!
(imitating gunfire)
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- [Joel] New from
the Franklin Mint.
- [Crow] Oh, he's
sendin' 'em a message.
He's saying, hey,
my emblem came off.
(heroic music)
♪ Ken and his friend are free ♪
♪ They're free together ♪
♪ They're free to
be you and me ♪
- [Crow] I'm blind,
I'm blind, help me.
(shouting)
- [Tom] Take a picture
of us, we're posing.
- [Crow] It'll last longer.
- Ken!
- [Tom] Nice teeth.
- Captain, Ken made it.
- [Joel] Captain Ken made it?
- What about the Caesar officer?
- [Tammy] He's there too.
- I knew he'd pull it off.
- [Crow] Now let's
break out the liquor.
Oh, I drank it all.
- [Dan] Ken you did it.
- [Tammy] Ken!
- [Joe] Good work, son.
- [Rocky] Welcome back, Ken.
- [Tammy] I was so worried
about you, oh, Ken!
(clears throat)
- [Colonel] Let me
introduce myself.
- [Tom] I'm a man
of wealth and taste.
- Sir, welcome Colonel.
I'm Captain Joe, welcome aboard.
- [Joel] This is my fleet
of Elvis impersonators.
- Yes, sir!
- [Crow] Join me for Up
All Night, all C movies.
- [Tom] Bacchus-3 will be back
in Sweet Sweet
Back's Badass Song.
It's a movie.
Bye!
(soft music)
- [Joel] I'll wet 'em.
♪ Say good-bye to
Rita's Star Trek stuff ♪
♪ And it's out of focus ♪
♪ In my pocket it will stay ♪
- [Tom] No to be continued?
- [Crow] Ah, no!
- [Tom] No, get us
outta here, Joel!
Oh, terrible.
- Well this one over
here dispatches a special
aquatic version of
Greenpeace's Rainbow Warriors
to go out and do
battle against the man.
- Heavy, rave on Joel,
hype it up buddy.
- Right, well, this one over
here, well heaven forbid
the robot that may try
to touch this button
or even brush against it,
for that robot would
become my personal slave.
No robot can venture
too far out of the ship,
especially if such a robot
were to disguise his true
identity from me in
the form of feather.
Heaven help that poor
robot that may try that.
- Really, let me try.
Okay, here we go.
- No, no that would
be an abomination of
robots everywhere.
- Well, what's
that other one do?
- This is portion
control, next question.
- Okay, how 'bout that one?
- This does any number of
phantasmagorical wondrous things
the most benign being
that Tommy Jeffries
who lives in Belize and
dad works on an oil derrick
gets a tasty pudding snack.
- [Both Robots] What a rush.
That Joel Robinson is one bad--
- Shut your mouth.
- I was talkin' about Joel.
- That's all right.
Anyway, we've got a letter
here form David A. DiCordova.
- Way to go, kid.
- Thanks, Mr. Crow.
- And he writes in to
answer to the question
of what is the cool thing
that we did a while back.
And he writes, let's put
this up on still story.
He writes "Dear Gentlemen
and Gypsy, concerning
"the cool thing, my
guess is that you saw
"a time portal
floating in space.
"Taking into account
that overall the crew is
"against imperialism,
jingoism, church state as one,
"fascism, exploitation, racism,
"in short all those
ideals held dear
"by our world leaders
here on earth.
"I'd venture to say
this time portal
"showed mankind
living in peace."
Well, we're sorry
David A. DiCordova from
Seattle, Washington.
But this was the cool thing.
Mexican stoplight candy.
- Oh, what a burn.
- Whatta you think, sirs?
- Now this to me is good TV.
Being genetically altered
on cable television.
Ann Dillard will be out
to discuss her new book
and then later on, Topol,
that robust star of Fiddler
on the Roof will be out.
- [Clayton] Frank, why
are we off the air?
- [Frank] Uh, I thought it
was time to push the button.
Besides, don't you
wanna get started
genetically altering
Jack Perkins?
- [Clayton] Look, we don't
go off until I say we go off.
Now run down to the storeroom
and get that spare head.
I've got a mad posh
to give Jack Perkins
the head of Vivian Vance.
- [Frank] Sorry, Sarge.
- [Jack] Ah, Vivian Vance.
(screams)
(soft music)
(laughs)
- You're stuck here.